Guide to the Sapolsky and Slobodien Architecture collection 1948-1985 PR 439
New-York Historical Society
Sapolsky and Slobodien Architecture collection
1948-1985
New-York Historical Society
Sapolsky & Slobodien (active 1948-1986)
PR 439
13 Linear feet in 12 record cartons and 1 flat box
This collection consists of correspondence, blueprints, drawings, permit applications, and invoices from the commercial architectural firm of Sapolsky and Slobodien, based in New York City and active approximately 1948-1986.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by subject into five series:
Series I: Home Life Insurance
Series II: Lazere
Series III: Longchamps
Series IV: Luchow's Restaurant
Series V: Other Buildings
Each series is arranged chronologically, aligning with the original order as determined by the folder numbering system: the first 2 digits of the number on each folder denote the year of the records contained within it.
Biographical / Historical
The New York City architecture firm of Sapolsky and Slobodien was active from about 1948 to about 1986. From their office at 202 West 40th Street, architects Thomas Sapolsky (1911-1994) and Kassel Slobodien (1912-1986) designed mainly commercial spaces. A major client was the Home Life Insurance Company. Sapolsky and Slobodien did extensive renovations of the Home Life Insurance Company's landmark building at 253-256 Broadway, and designed the company's branch offices across the United States.
Access Restrictions
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquisition information is not available.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of records from the architectural firm of Sapolsky and Slobodien, based in New York City and active approximately 1948-1986. The records, which include correspondence, blueprints, drawings, permit applications, and invoices, document Sapolsky and Slobodien's design and renovation of commerical spaces such as office buildings, restaurants, and shops in New York City and across the country. The bulk of the collection is material related to the firm's work for the Home Life Insurance Company.
Architectural firms -- New York (State) -- New York.; Architecture, American -- 20th century -- Designs and plans.; Office buildings -- Designs and plans.; Architectural records.; Sapolsky, Thomas, 1911-1994; Slobodien, Kassel, 1912-1986; Home Life Insurance Company; Longchamps (Restaurant: New York, N.Y.); Luchow's (Restaurant: New York, N.Y.)
- Series I: Home Life Insurance, 1962-1983
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, blueprints, drawings, permit applications, and invoices related to Sapolsky and Slobodien's work for the Home Life Insurance Company
  - 64-24 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Exterior Sign and 15th Floor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-6 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 14th Floor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-35 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 2nd Floor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-36 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 3rd Floor, Rosen, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-42 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Vertical Conveyor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-53 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Lobby Desk, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-A-55 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 2nd Floor Decor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-61 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 5th Floor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-64 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Silberman, 3rd Floor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-65 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Mr. Kelly's Suite, part 9th Floor, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 64-68 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 9th Floor, Eleford, 1964 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-5 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 14th Floor, Goldrich, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-14 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, part of 3rd Floor, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-18 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Feinberg and Lusterman, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-A-28 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 12th Floor, Law Library, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-36 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 9th Floor Rear, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-37 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 9th Floor Mintz Suite, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-46 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC Arenson and Gelinas Suite, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-54 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, New Elevators, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-57 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 4th Floor Medical Department, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 65-70 Home Life Insurance Co., Vaults, 1965 (Offsite-box 1)
  - 66-4 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 4th Floor North, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 66-16 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 7th Floor, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 66-31 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 5th Floor South, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 66-40 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 12th Floor, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 66-41 and 66-62 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Torchin 9th Floor, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 66-46 and 66-53 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 8th Floor West Epstein, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 66-61 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Fifth Floor North, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 66-67 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 8th Floor Front Sullivan, 1966 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-A-8 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, 8th Floor Men's Room, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-9 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 13th Floor, Front, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-A-11 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 8th Floor Rear, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-15 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 16th Floor, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-17 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 7th Floor North Zelnick Suite, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-A-22 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, 6th Floor, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-A-26 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, 14th Floor Corridor, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-35 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, Air Conditioning Survey, 7th Floor and Cooling Tower, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-39 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Part 14th Floor Levidow, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-44 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 6th Floor Computer Center, 1967 (Offsite-box 2)
  - 67-49 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, 14th Floor Jasper (Offsite-box 2)
  - 68-A-7 Home Life Insurance Co. 2 Penn Plaza NYC, 9th and 25th Floors, 1968 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 68-A-32 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, Sidewalk, 1968 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 68-33 Home Life Insurance Co. 110 East 59th Street NYC, 1968 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 68-A-36 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 10th Floor, 1968 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 68-A-41 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Sub-Cellar, 1968 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 69-5 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Part Cellar Plan, 1969 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 69-13 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, Agency Work, 1969 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 69-18 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 14th Floor Farber, 1969 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 69-43 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 15th Floor, 1969 (Offsite-box 3)
  - 70-19 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, 2nd Floor Dining, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 70-24 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 7th Floor North Zelnick, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 70-25 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 11th Floor, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 70-30 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 7th Floor, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 70-A-35 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 11th Floor, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 70-A-38 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Sub-Cellar, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 70-12 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 4th Floor Medical, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 70-14 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 10th Floor President's Office and Board Room, 1970 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 71-1 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 12th Floor Pension Sales, 1971 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 71-15 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Part of 11th Floor, 1971 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 71-18 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway, 13th Floor, 1971 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-1 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 6th Floor Computer, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-9 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Rental Plan for Branches, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-15 Home Life Insurance Co. NYC, Sidewalk Repair, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-19 Home Life Insurance Co. New Orleans, LA, Agency, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-20 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 8th Floor Segal, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-22 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 6th Floor Computer Room, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-30 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Agency Plans Typical, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 72-38 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Sub-Cellar, 1972 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 73-13 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 11th Floor, 1973 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 73-22 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway, NYC, 11th Floor Broadway Front, 1973 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 73-46 Home Life Insurance Co. 15 Murray Street, NYC 12th Floor, 1973 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-1 Home Life Insurance Co. New Jersey Ford Agency, Springfield NJ, 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-9 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 110 East 59th Street NYC, 34th Floor, 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-11 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 14th Floor, 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-14 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 6th Floor (Co-2 system), 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-19 Home Life Insurance Co. 253-256 Broadway NYC, Survey for Local Law #5 of 1973, 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-22 Home Life Insurance Co., Chicago Agency, 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-29 Home Life Insurance Co. Hicksville Agency 120 Bethpage Road, 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 74-A-31 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 2nd Floor Public Assembly, 1974 (Offsite-box 4)
  - 75-1 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 999 Brickell Avenue Miami, Florida, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-5 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 2600 Douglas Road Coral Gables, Florida, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-A-8 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency San Diego, CA, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-11 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Milburn, NJ, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-14 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 9th Floor, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-18 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 5th Floor, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-23 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 12th Floor, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-26 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Sub-Cellar Vent, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-29 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Orlando, Florida, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-30 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Woodbury, Long Island, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-34 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Florham Park, NJ, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-39 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Detroit, MI, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 75-43 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Longchamps, 1975 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 76-1 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Denver, CO, 1976 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 76-2 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC 6th Floor, 1976 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 76-9 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Atlanta, GA, 1976 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 76-12 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Baltimore, MD, 1976 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 76-13 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Cast Iron Front, 1976 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 76-19 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC 10th Floor, 1976 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 76-24 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Houston, TX, 1976 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-2 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Greensboro, NC, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-3 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Cherry Hill, NJ, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-4 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Dadeland, FL, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-5 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Rochester, NY, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-6 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Lincolnwood, IL, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-8 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Clifton, NJ, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-9 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 825 3rd Avenue, 20th Floor, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-12 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 & 256 Broadway NYC, 8th Floor, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-13 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway, 2nd Floor Dining Rooms, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-14 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Walnut Creek, CA, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-15 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Bloomfield, CT, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-17 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Tampa, Florida, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-18 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Amendment 2nd Floor, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-19 Home Life Insurance Co.256 Broadway NYC, 2nd Floor Personnel, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-20 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Washington, DC, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-22 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Buffalo, NY, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-28 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Lake Success, NY, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 77-29 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Lansing, MI, 1977 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-2 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Pittsburgh, PA, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-3 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 6th Floor Computer, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-5 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Pittsburg, PA, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-6 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Pasadena, CA, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-7 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Buffalo, NY, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-9 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Colonie, NY, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-10 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Newtown, CT, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-11 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 253 Broadway NYC, Conveyor to 9 Murray Street, 1978 (Offsite-box 5)
  - 78-12 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency San Francisco, CA, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-13 Home Life Insurance Co. 253-256 Broadway NYC, 9th and 14th Floors, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-14 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Newport Beach, CA, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-15 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Sacramento, CA, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-16 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Greensboro, SC, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-17 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Buffalo, NY, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-18 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 10th Floor President's Office and Board Room, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-19 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 10th Floor Hall of Fame, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-21 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Wichita, KS, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-22 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Telephone Panels, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-25 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 6th Floor Computer, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-26 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Skokie, IL, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-27 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Erie, PA, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-28 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Atlanta, GA, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-30 Home Life Insurance Co. 253-256 Broadway NYC, Research for Building Use, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-31 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Woodbury, NY, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-32 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 13th Floor Storage, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-35 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Dayton, OH, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-37 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Basic Agency Layout, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-38 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Independence, OH, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 78-39 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Possible Rental, 1978 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-1 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 10th Floor Office, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-2 Home Life Insurance Co. 100 Church Street NYC, 4th Floor, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-3 Home Life Insurance Co. 253-256 Broadway NYC, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-4 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Lincolnwood, IL, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-5 Home Life Insurance Co. 100 Church Street NYC 9th Floor, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-6 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Telephone Equipment Installation 10th & 11th Floors, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-7 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Electric Files 4th Floor, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-8 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 5th Floor, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-9 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Tulsa, OK, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-11 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Newtown, CT, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-13 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Cast Iron on Front, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-17 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Clayton, MO, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-18 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Hartsdale, NY, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-22 Home Life Insurance Co. 100 Church Street NYC 4th Floor "E.S.P.", 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-26 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency San Francisco, CA, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-23 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Rochester, NY, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-29 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Edina, MN, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 79-31 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, New Desk in Lobby, 1979 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-1 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Arcadia, CA, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-3 Home Life Insurance Co. 253-256 Broadway NYC, 6th, 8th and 11th Floors, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-4 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Chicago, IL Presidents' Plaza, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-5 Home Life Insurance Co. 253-256 Broadway NYC, Civic Center Historic District, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-8 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 2nd Floor Cafeteria, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-9 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Chicago, IL, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-10 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Indianapolis, IN, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-13 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Daytona, FL, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-15 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Springfield, IL, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-17 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Syracuse, NY, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-18 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency South Miami, FL, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-19 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Wichita, KS, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-20 Home Life Insurance Co. 253-256 Broadway NYC, Local Law #5/1973, 1973-1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-22 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Tallahassee, FL, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-23 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Dallas, TX, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-24 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Chicago, IL, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-29 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Pittsburgh,PA, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-30 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Green Village, NJ, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-33 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Wellesley Hills, MA, 1980 (Offsite-box 6)
  - 80-35 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Computer Installation, 1980 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 80-A-36 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Bloomfield, CT, 1980 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 80-A-37 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Syracuse, NY, 1980 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-A-1 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Fort Lauderdale, FL, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-4 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Towson, MD, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-10 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Fairlawn, NJ, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-11 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Greensboro, NC, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-13 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Telephone Equipment, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-14 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Salt Lake City, UT, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-15 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Bloomfield, CT, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-18 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Peoria, IL, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-19 Home Life Insurance Co. 9-15 Murray Street NYC, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-22 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency West Palm Beach, FL, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-23 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Chicago ,IL, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-A-24 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 2nd Floor Emergency Lighting, Library, Lounge, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-A-25 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Palm Beach Gardens, FL, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-A-26 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency, 825 Third Avenue NYC, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-A31 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-A-32 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Seattle, WA, 1921 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 81-A-35 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Fort Lauderdale, FL, 1981 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-1 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Newport News, VA, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-2 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Rockford, IL, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-3 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-5 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Virginia Beach, VA, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-7 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 825 Third Avenue NYC, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-8 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 12th Floor, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-9/10 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, Coffee Machines, Library, Lounge, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-12 Home Life Insurance Agency Wellesley, MA, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-14 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Hauppauge, NY, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-15 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, Plymouth Shop, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-16 Home Life Insurance Co. 9-15 Murray Street NYC, Print Shop, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-17 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Green Village, NJ, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-18 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 770 Lexington Avenue NYC, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-19 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Lake Success, NY, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-20 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Clayton, MO, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-22 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Overland Park, KS, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-23 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC Cast Iron Inner Court, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A-27 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Memphis, TN, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 82-A28/29/30 Home Life Insurance Co. 256 Broadway NYC, 1982 (Offsite-box 7)
  - 83-A-1 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Florham Park, NJ, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-2 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Bethesda, MD, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-4 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Green Village, NJ, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-5 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 9-15 Murray Street NYC, Printing Equipment, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-6 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency San Francisco, CA, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-8 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency 30 Vesey Street, NYC, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-9 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Wellesley Hills, MA, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-11 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Pittsburgh, PA, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-12 Home Life Insurance Co. Agency Syracuse, NY, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - 83-A-13/14/16/17 Home Life Insurance Co. 253 Broadway NYC, 1983 (Offsite-box 8)
  - Billing Records - Home Life Insurance Co., 1962-1983 (Offsite-box 8)
- Series II: Lazere, 1971-1985
  This series contains correspondence, drawings, permit applications, and invoices related to Sapolsky and Slobodien's work for the Lazere Financial Corporation.
  - 71-19, Lazere 26 West Mt. Eden Avenue, Bronx, 1971 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 78-24 Lazere Financial, 60 East 42nd Street, 37th Floor, NYC, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 79-30 M. Lazere Office, Miami, Florida, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 80-11 Lazere 1040 Avenue of the Americas, NYC, 1980 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 80-28 Lazere Financial Corp. 60 East 42nd Street, 37th Floor, NYC, 1980 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 81-A-37 Lazere 60 East 42nd Street, Safe, 37th Floor, NYC, 1981 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 82-A-6 Lazere Chicago, Illinois, 1982 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 82-A-11 Lazere Financial Corp. 444 Brickell Avenue, Miami, Florida, 1982 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 84-A-3 Lazere Financial Corp., 444 Brickell Avenue, Miami, Florida, 1984 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 85-2 Lazere Financial Corp. 60 East 42nd Street, 37th Floor, NYC, 1985 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 85-A-4 Lazere Financial Corp. 60 East 42nd Street, 13th and 37th Floors, NYC, 1985 (Offsite-box 9)